# CHRISTOPHER HUNLEY

#### **CONTACT**

8

Alvaton, KY 42122

(**[**])

4199617435

 $\overline{\phantom{a}}$ 

cshunley21@gmail.com

# WEBSITES, PORTFOLIOS, PROFILES

- https://www.linkedin.com/mwlite /in/chris-hunley-93326021a
- https://github.com/cman0493

#### **SKILLS**

- Multi-tasking skill
- Interpersonal ability
- Time management strength
- Proficiency in Microsoft Office
- Leadership
- Troubleshooting
- Web development projects
- HTML experience
- Website optimization
- Project Management
- HTML
- JavaScript
- CSS
- Technical Support

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

 Web Development, Common Wealth Coders - 6 months

#### **EDUCATION**

Expected in December 2021

Certification Coding/IT Tech

Commonwealth Coders, Bowling Green, KY

May 2015

Bachelor's English Literature

Ball State University, Muncie, IN

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Solution-driven Junior Web Developer adept at contributing to highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions and determining customer satisfaction. Proven experience developing consumer-focused websites using HTML, CSS, PHP and JavaScript. Built products for desktop and mobile app users over 6 months, meeting highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices and speed. Designed and developed web applications across multiple APIs, third-party integrations and databases.

### **WORK HISTORY**

Manager Trainee Cook Out Restaurants, Bowling Green, KY 05/2019 - 01/2020

- Established and administered annual budget with controls to prevent overages, minimize burn rate and support sustainability objectives.
- Devised processes to boost long-term business success and increase profit levels.
- Maximized resource utilization during projects to uphold strict budget targets.
- Applied performance data to evaluate and improve operations, target current business conditions and forecast needs.
- Pursued every opportunity to learn about business at all levels and improve team member support.
- Conferred with customers each day to maintain current understanding of needs and preferences, resolve issues and promote brand loyalty.
- Explained services and products to customers in friendly and engaging way.
- Planned and implemented team projects to accomplish objectives.
- Stayed up to date on changing product and service options to provide top-notch support to customers and employees.

# Shift Supervisor Walgreens, Scottsville, KY 01/2019-05-2019

- Established effective employee schedules and delegated tasks to take advantage of individual abilities and meet expected demands.
- Built performance-oriented culture with satisfied, hardworking employees by clearly highlighting employee success and developing leaders from within.

- Conducted weekly inspections to evaluate operational activities and implement timely resolutions for diverse concerns.
- Conducted routine inspections of incoming materials to check quality and compliance with established product specifications.
- Prepared, calibrated and monitored production machinery to maintain optimal production levels and consistently achieve daily targets.
- Evaluated employee skills and knowledge regularly, training and mentoring individuals with lagging skills.
- Minimized resource and time losses by addressing employee or production issue directly and implementing timely solutions.
- Consulted with HR teams to identify and onboard optimal candidates for positions.
- Helped store management meet standards of service and quality in daily operations.

# Cashier Team Lead Ball State University Dining, Muncie, IN 10/2015 - 07/2017

- Quickly and accurately counted drawers at start and end of each shift.
- Monitored areas for security issues and safety hazards.
- Interpreted and enforced operating instructions, procedures and safety rules.
- Communicated with customers and team members to solve problems.
- Controlled merchandise zoning and monitored compliance with merchandising guidelines.
- Trained team members on cash register operation and cash handling.
- Generated routine reports and professional correspondence.
- Led opening and closing procedures and conducted cashier drops, cash control, and vault monitoring.
- Operated POS cash register and equipment to collect payments.